怎么样
How's it look?
到处是监控
Cameras everywhere.
是啊
Yeah, right.
大门
Big gates.
不好搞
Not good.
反正我们有好多开心果
Ah, well, we've got plenty of pistachios.
以下均为出演过詹姆斯·邦德系列电影的演员
- 康纳利  - 没错
-Connery. Yeah. -Yeah. Totally.
第二个呢
Second?
拉曾比
Lazenby.
- 拉曾比  - 对啊
-Lazenby? -Yeah.
这特么是谁啊
Who the fuck's that?
乔治·拉曾比啊
George Lazenby.
没听说过这人
No, never heard of him.
在康纳利之后
After Connery.
他拍了
He did, um,
第二部《女王密使》
Her Majesty's, uh, Secret Service.
- 是吗  - 就拍过一部007电影啊
-Mm-hmm? -Only did one film.
没看过  我得看一下
Never seen it. I'll have to see it.
- 很好看的  - 好
Yeah, it's good. Yeah, right.
他是澳大利亚人
He's an Aussie.
- 澳大利亚人 - 对啊
-An Aussie? -Mm-hmm.
- 演邦德吗  - 澳洲版邦德啊
-Bond? -Aussie Bond, mate.
- 得了吧  - 真的啊
-Fuck off. -Yeah, serious.
才不是呢  不会有澳洲邦德啊
That's not right-- you can't have an Aussie Bond.
真的是澳洲人啊
No, he's Aussie.
- 是吗  - 是啊
-Really? -Yeah.
- 好的吧  - 嗯
-Yeah, right. -Mm-hmm.
- 这就两个了  - 嗯
-Okay. So that's two. -Yeah.
第三个呢
What about number three?
我不喜欢现在扮演邦德的那个人
I don't mind the guy playing him now.
叫什么啊
Mm-hmm. What's his name?
叫他么什么啊
What's his fucking name?
我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
嗯
Yeah.
- 不过他排第三  - 好吧  他第三
-He's number three, though. -Yeah, he's three.
好  第四呢
Right-o. Number four?
第四
Four...
我不喜欢摩尔
I didn't like Moore.
- 你不喜欢老罗杰吗  - 不喜欢
-Don't like the old Roger? -No.
- 不喜欢啊  - 对  太势利眼了
-Nah? -Nah, too snobby,
- 是吗  - 油嘴滑舌的
-Really? -polished, yeah.
- 是吗  - 我不喜欢他
-Yeah? -I didn't like him.
我挺喜欢老罗杰的
I like the old Roger.
- 不  不喜欢他  - 好吧
-Yeah, no, I didn't like him. -Okay.
那布鲁斯南呢
What about Brosnan?
不喜欢
No.
布鲁斯南排最后
No, I put Brosnan last.
- 布鲁斯南也不喜欢 - 排最后
-Don't like Brosnan? -Last.
- 真的啊  - 对
-Really? -Yeah.
好的吧
Yeah, all right.
所以我的排序是
Yeah, no, I'd go:
康纳利  拉曾比
Connery, Lazenby,
现在演邦德的那个人
guy playing him now...
- 嗯呢  - 道尔顿
-Mm-hmm. -um, Dalton,
摩尔
Moore...
- 布鲁斯南  - 好
-Brosnan. -All right.
我的是  康纳利
I got: Connery...
摩尔  布鲁斯南
Moore, Brosnan,
- 现在演邦德的那个人  - 嗯
-guy playing him now... -Mm-hmm.
- 道尔顿  - 不喜欢他
-Dalton. -Don't like him.
好吧
All right.
最棒的一个蝙蝠侠呢
Best Batman.
- 基顿  - 基顿  对
-Keaton. -Keaton. Yeah.
我是蝙蝠侠
"I'm Batman."
开门了
H... Here we are.
好
Okay.
停到这里
Pull in there.
要杀谁
Which one's the prez?
穿浅色夹克的那人
Guy in the light-colored jacket.
另一个呢
And the VP?
他拥抱的那个  光头
That guy he's hugging now-- the bald head.
好的
Yeah, right.
是他么的丹尼尔·克雷格
It's fucking Daniel Craig.
就是了
Ah. That's it.
先生
中间人
第二季
第三集
翻译： 岛岛
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
翻译： 十二点前要睡觉
加油啊  加油啊
Put the thingy on! Put the...
翻译： 噬魂
校对： 岛岛
左拐
Go left!
特效： 转轮手枪
好
Yeah!
时间轴： 麦斯
好了  最后一个
All right, last one.
这个要打中啊
You need to get this one.
- 是吗  - 最后一枪了
-Yeah? -Last one.
- 好的 -  准备好了吗
-All right. -Ready?
祈祷吧
Start praying.
他很厉害啊
He's good.
你想要哪个
What do you want?
- 要那个吧  - 好的
-Uh, that one, please. -No worries.
给你
-There you go.
- 开心啦 - 嗯
-Happy? -Yeah.
我们圣诞节要干嘛
What are we doing for Christmas?
你想干嘛
What do you want to do?
我家人都会
Well, my family
去我爸妈家吃午饭啊
are going to my folks for lunch...
- 嗯  - 我想问问你
-Yeah. -and I was wondering
和布鲁斯还有布里特
if you and Bruce and Britt...
想不想一起去
wanted to come.
好  我问下布鲁斯
Yeah, I'll ask Brucey.
不过我和布里特肯定会去的
But Britt and I will definitely come.
好
Okay.
- 小姑娘们  要不要冰淇淋  - 要的
-Girls, you want an ice cream? -Yeah! -Yeah!
- 要的  - 厉害了啊
- Yes. -Yeah, that's a surprise.
- 我要一个巧克力球  - 好
-Let me get a scoop of chocolate. -Right.
两个球  好的  装满吧
Two scoops. Why not? Fill it up.
- 两个球吗  - 对啊
-Two? -Yeah.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
好了给你
And there you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 打扰一下  - 嗯
-Uh, excuse me? -Yeah?
我这杯要了两个球啊
I asked for two scoops.
是啊  是两个球啊
Oh, yeah, there's two scoops there.
那怎么两杯一模一样多呢
How come they're the same size, then?
你看啊
-See?
这杯里有一个球  对吧
Well, there's one scoop in this cup, right?
- 嗯  - 然后这杯有两个球
-Yeah. -And two scoops in this cup?
- 嗯 - 怎么会一样大呢
-Yeah. -So how come they're the same size, then?
- 啊  抱歉  - 这两杯的冰淇淋是一样多的
-Oh. No, sorry, I... -There-There's as much in this one as this one.
是啊  我把两个冰淇淋球往下压了压
Right, I pushed the two scoops down more
这样就能装下了啊
so that they'd both fit into the cup.
- 没事了啊  - 他敲我们竹杠啊
-Just don't worry about it. -What? It's a fucking rip-off.
里面的冰淇淋球都是一样大的
I put the same-size scoops in there.
你放的都是一样大的吗
You put the same-size scoops in there?
- 是啊  - 我他么觉得不是啊
-Yes. -I don't fucking think so, mate.
你看啊
-Look. -
两个球跟一个球一样高
Scoops. Same height.
是啊
SERVER: Mm-hmm.
我说了  我把两个球的往下压了
Yeah, um, like I was saying, I pushed it down, so...
- 这是两勺吗  - 是啊
Two scoops. Yeah, yeah.
- 两个球的应该比一个球的多啊  - 嗯
-One still should be bigger. -Mm-hmm.
如果您不满意的话
If you're n... if you're not happy...
- 再给我添两勺  - 好
-Give me two scoops. -Okay.
脑子有毛病吧
Fucking wrong with this guy.
- 好像聋子  - 真的很抱歉
-Deaf or something. -I'm really sorry about that.
再给您来一勺
There's another scoop.
这样好多了
All right, that's better.
你懂我意思吧  一勺两勺的
You get what I mean, right, about the scoops?
嗯  没问题的
Oh, yeah, totally. It's completely fine.
- 一切都好  - 嗯
-Yeah, all good. -Mm-hmm.
行了  走吧
All right, let's go.
你看什么看  找事吗  傻屌
You got a problem, mate?
是你想找事吧
Yeah, mate. Would you like one, would you?
那你来啊
Well, come on.
- 来啊  - 雷
-Let's go. - Ray.
- 怎么  - 不值当的
-Huh? - It's not worth it.
- 来啊  - 撒比
-Well, come on. -Eh...
我就知道你没种  娘炮
Yeah, that's what I thought. Fag.
要什么味的  姑娘们
Uh, what do you want, girls?
- 什么口味  - 你要什么
-What flavor? -Eh? What do you want?
我要咸焦糖
I want salted caramel.
- 咸焦糖  - 对
-Salted caramel? -Yeah.
我要薄荷巧克力屑的
I want mint choc chip.
- 薄荷巧克力屑的我也喜欢啊  - 对呀
-Mint choc-- that's my favorite. -Yeah.
- 要几个冰淇淋球  - 祝你愉快
-How many scoops you want? -Have a good night.
爸爸
Dad?
- 天啊  对不起  - 别打艾丽啊
-Oh. God. Oh! Sorry, it's... -Don't hit Ally!
没事的宝贝  没事的
No, darling, it's okay. It's okay. It's, um...
- 我们没事啊  就是  - 你干嘛打她啊
-We're okay. We're just... -Why were you hitting her?
- 不不不不不不  没事的  - 我不是在打她
-No, no, no, no. It's okay. -I... I wasn't hitting.
- 不是的  - 我不是  我不是  不是的  我们只是随便玩玩  亲爱的
-No... -I wasn't. I wasn't. No, we're just mucking around, love.
只是随便玩玩  就是为了好玩而已
Just-just... just mucking around, just playful.
- 啥事都没有  - 你刚才在干嘛
-And it's all right. -What were you doing?
我们刚刚在做爱
We were having sex.
噢  天呐
Oh, Jesus.
一种儿童性教育的隐晦的比喻
妈妈跟你谈过小鸟和蜜蜂的故事了吗  亲爱的
Um, has Mum had the birds and the bees chat with you, love?
- 什么  - 关于性的谈话
-What? -The sex talk.
- 妈妈有跟你谈过性话题了吗  - 没有
-Has Mum talked to you about sex? -No.
好吧  我们  我们  我们
Okay. Well, we... We'll... we'll...
我们之后会谈的  好吗
We'll have a talk about it, okay?
要不你先回你房间吧  然后我们
Why don't you just go to your room, and we'll...?
我一会就过去  好吗
I'll come in in a minute, all right?
给我们点时间
Just give us a minute.
我的个天
Ah, man. Mm.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
心脏病差点都出来了
Fucking heart attack.
好吧  所以
Okay. So...
当一个男人和一个女人相爱的时候
When a man and a woman love each other,
他们就会做爱
all right, they have sex.
好吗
Okay?
所以
So, um...
当他们做爱的时候
...when they have sex,
男人就会把他的阴茎
the man puts his penis...
- 你知道什么是阴茎吗  - 老爸
-You know what a penis is? -Dad.
好吧
Okay.
所以男人就会把他的阴茎
So, the man takes his penis,
然后他把它
and he puts it
放到女人的阴道里
inside the woman's vagina.
什么  为啥
What? Why?
因为  这样才能生小孩
Well, 'cause that's how you make a baby.
所以  你知道  呃
So, do you know what, um...
你知道什么是睾丸吗
do you know what testicles are?
蛋蛋吗
Balls?
蛋蛋  对的  没错  所以  在男性的睾丸里
Balls, yeah. Okay. So, in the man's balls,
有个叫做精子的东西
there's things called sperm.
- 懂吗  - 好的
-Okay? -Okay.
然后它们有点像  呃  有点像小鱼苗
And they're kind of like, um, like little fish.
- 小鱼  - 嗯  - 不
-Fish? -Mm. - No.
不  它们比较像小蝌蚪
Nah, they're more like, um, tadpoles.
你的蛋蛋里有小蝌蚪吗
You've got tadpoles in your balls?
它们只是像小蝌蚪  但是比小蝌蚪还小点
They're kind of like tadpoles, but they're smaller.
懂了吗
Okay?
所以  反正  男人和女人发生性行为的时候
So, anyway, when the man and the woman have sex, right,
精子  也就是小蝌蚪
the sperm-- the little tadpoles--
皮皮节
年度医学美肤大促 9.9-9.29
新氧
医美
■
新人199元免单
○
-
就会从男人的阴茎里游出来
swim out of the man's penis, right,
然后跑到女人的阴道里面
and go into the woman's vagina.
然后它们就会游泳
And then they swim
游到
up into...
女人的输卵道里去
the woman's... tummy.
那里有个卵子  卵子就在那里
Mm. There's an egg. Where there's an egg there.
- 蛋  - 没错  不不不
-An egg? -Yeah. No, it's...
不是那种硬壳鸡蛋  不是像
it's not a... it's not a hard egg. It's not like...
不是像鸡蛋那种  是软软的蛋
Not like a chicken egg. It's-it's a soft egg.
然后  在那里
And there's, like,
大概有几百万个精子  好吗
millions of these sperm, okay?
然后游的最快的精子
So, the sperm that swims the fastest
百万之中最快的那一个
out of all those millions, right,
是第一个跑到卵子旁边去的精子
is the first one that gets to the egg,
然后它们的结合就会产生宝宝了
and that's the one that makes the baby.
所以  当你还是个精子的时候  你游的最快
So, when you were a sperm, you swam the fastest.
如果我是游得最快的精子
So, if I was the fastest sperm,
为啥我现在不擅长游泳呢
how come I'm not a good swimmer now?
- 好吧  - 等等  所以
-Well... -Wait. So, hang on.
我是从你的蛋蛋里出来的吗
I came from your balls?
你有一半来源于我的蛋蛋
Half of you came from my balls.
只是一半的你是来源于我的蛋蛋
Half-half of you came from my balls,
然后另一半是来源于你妈咪的卵巢
and the other half came from your mum's tummy.
- 那也太奇怪了  - 嗯
-That's weird. -Mm.
所以你们想给我生个妹妹是吗
So, are you gonna make a sister for me?
不  我们还没这个打算
Uh, no, we're not planning to. No.
那你们为啥要做爱啊
Why are you doing sex, then?
因为  它让人愉悦
Um... 'cause it feels nice.
恶心
Gross!
也没那么糟糕  是有点恶心
- It's not that bad.  - It's a bit gross.
灯光亮起
* Lights out... *
你最近如何  亲爱的
How you going, love?
还不错  需要点什么吗
G'day. What can I do you for?
来几块点心  谢了  亲爱的
Just a couple of dimmies. Thanks, love.
好的
Okay.
所以  你今天过得怎么样
So, how's your day going?
挺好的  你呢
It's all right. How's yours?
噢  你懂的  一如既往
Oh, you know. Same old, same old.
- 是啊  - 无聊
-Yeah. -Boring.
给  一共6.8澳币  谢了
There you go. That's $6.80, thanks.
找零留着吧  亲爱的  好吧
Keep the change, love, all right?
谢了
Aw, thanks.
我们一起走过这一切
* Together we'll get through *
我没有时间去
* I don't have the time... *
我保证  亲爱的宝贝你
* I promise, baby, you *
紧紧的抱住我
* Hold on to me tight *
我会永远待在你身边
* I'm hanging by your side... *
来了
Here we go.
斯蒂芬  你最近咋样啊  亲爱的
Hey, Steph. How are you, doll?
- 还不错  你呢  - 很好
-G'day. Not bad. You? -Good.
- 很好  - 我挺好的  亲爱的
-Good. -I'm doing good, love.
- 你想喝点什么吗  伙计  - 要的  一杯柠檬
-You want a drink, mate? -Yeah, a lemon i...
柠檬冰茶  兄弟
lemon iced tea, man.
雷
Ray?
你怎么样啊  兄弟
How are you, mate?
难以置信啊
I don't believe it.
- 雷·休史密斯  - 是啊
-Ray Shoesmith. -Yeah.
你最近怎么样  还好吗
How you been? All right?
天呐  这也太棒了吧  兄弟
Jesus. I'm real good, mate.
天呐  真是
Geez, it's good to... Oh.
- 兄弟  能见到你真的太好了  - 是啊  我也是  维尼
-Mate, it's good to see you. -Yeah. Same, Vinnie.
- 不  认真的  我真心的  - 是啊  是啊  是啊
-No, really. Seriously. -Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- 能见到太他妈好了  - 是啊 我也一样
-Fucking good to see you. -Yeah, same, mate. Yeah.
什么  你住在这附近的吧  是吗
What the...? You-you live around here, do you?
- 没错  差不多那条路再走十分钟就到了  - 挺好  挺好
-Yeah, just about ten minutes down the road. -Nice, nice.
- 你在住在这附近吗  - 是啊  是啊
-You around here, too, eh?  - Yeah, yeah.
- 听着  呃  保利  兄弟  - 是啊
-Hey, listen, uh, Pauly, mate. -Yeah.
保利的事情  我真的感觉太遗憾了
Yeah. I was real sorry to hear about Pauly.
- 是啊  - 我真的感觉很惋惜
-Oh, yeah. -I was real sorry to hear
- 关于那件事  兄弟  -  是啊  谢了  兄弟
-about that, mate. -Yeah. Thanks, mate.
我本来是会去参加葬礼的  但是我当时在海外
Now, I would've come to the funeral, I was overseas.
- 没关系的  没事  - 他是个好小伙  但是
-Yeah, no, it's all right. -He was a good bloke, but...
- 谢谢你  是啊  是个好小伙  - 抱歉
-Thank you. Yeah. Great bloke. -Yeah, sorry.
- 没事没事  - 话说回来  你来这买什么
-Yeah. yeah. -Yeah. Anyway, so what you got there?
- 你买了啥 点心  - 点心  兄弟
-What you...? Dimmies. -Dimmies, mate.
- 是啊  - 点心确实不容错过  兄弟
-Yeah. -Ah, can't go past the dimmies, mate.
- 那可不  - 嘿  嘿  听着
-Surely can't. -Hey. Hey, listen.
你试过香肠卷吗
Have you tried the sausage rolls?
- 没有  我还没试过  - 操  嘿  斯蒂芬
-Uh, no. No, I haven't. -Oh, fuck. Hey, Steph.
这个老伙计  他从来没尝过你的香肠卷
Old mate here-- he's never tried one of your sausage rolls.
- 马上来  维尼  - 我来付钱  好吧
-Coming right up, Vinnie. -I'll pay for it. Yeah?
- 好  - 好吧  我
-Yeah. -All right. I...
听起来似乎是我在搞推销
It might sound like I'm carrying on,
但说实话  这些都是她每天新鲜制作的
but seriously, she makes them fresh here every day.
是全美最好的香肠卷  我发誓
They're the best sausage rolls in the country, I swear to God.
- 是吗  - 放着吧先
-Oh, yeah? -Put that down there...
- 下次我会试试的  兄弟  我得先走了  - 好吧
-I'll give it a crack, mate. I got to run. -All right.
是啊  我已经迟到了  很高兴能遇到你
Yeah, I'm late already. Good to see you.
- 真的很棒  很好  -  是  是  是
-Real good. Real good. -Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- 你状态不错啊  - 你也是啊  没老呢
-You look good. -You, too. You haven't aged.
- 好的  保重  - 好
-Yeah. Look after yourself. -Well, yeah.
- 能见到你真是太高兴了  - 回头联系啊
-It's real good to see you, mate. -Talk to you soon.
你知道  有些数字加起来的结果对不上
Now, some of those numbers aren't gonna add up exactly,
- 但是我觉得  - 有些
-but I think... -Some of 'em?
- 你知道该怎么做的  - 是啊
-You know what to do. -Yeah.
- 有一些  就一点  - 是啊
-Some of 'em. Couple of 'em. -Yeah.
就几个数字  嘿  兄弟
Couple of 'em. Hi, mate.
- 你还好吗  - 挺好的
-You all right? -Yeah, good.
- 你要在这待一会吗  - 是啊
-You sticking around for a bit? -Yeah.
我想跟你谈个事情  你懂的
I want to talk to you about something, you know.
- 好  - 你最近如何  兄弟
-All right. -How you doing, man?
- 还好  - 雷
-Yeah. -Ray.
- 纳西尔  - 我们可得好好聊聊了  好吗
-Nasir. -We got to have a chat, all right?
我一会再来找你
I'll catch you later.
- 就是那个男的吗  - 不  兄弟  得了吧
-Is that the guy? -No, mate. Come on.
- 是那个人吗  - 走吧
-Is that the guy? -Let's go.
回答我
Answer me!
我可得让你尝尝失去的滋味
I'm gonna teach you about loss.
你说什么
Excuse me?
- 去干你的活  拜托了  - 我现在记住你的脸了
-Get to work, please now. -I know your face now.
- 去干活  雷  - 我要让你尝尝失去的滋味
-Get to work, Ray! -Gonna teach you about loss!
他是达沃尔的兄弟  是不是
Davros' brother, was it?
你他妈把他带到这干嘛
Why the fuck would you bring him in here?
好吧  我知道  我知道
Yeah, I know, I know.
听着  他说的那些废话
Hey, listen, um, that shit he said--
别担心
don't worry about that.
他就是有点心烦意乱
He's just... he's just upset, you know?
他是罪犯吗
Is he a crim?
不  他是名会计
No. No, he's an accountant.
他在帮我做账
He's been helping me with the books.
我甚至都不记得
I can't even remember
上一次我上床是什么时候了
the last time I got laid.
有多久了
How long's it been?
该死
Oh, shit.
也许有一年半
Year and a half, maybe.
要是你需要
I could, uh,
我可以帮你组织一下
organize something for you, if you want.
我讨厌妓院
I hate knock shops.
不  我会叫个姑娘
No, I'd just get one of the girls from work
到你这来
to come pay you a visit.
也许吧
Maybe.
我能问你些事吗
Can I ask you something?
可以
Yeah.
当我不想再这样下去的时候
When I don't feel like doing any of this anymore,
你会帮我吗
will you help me?
帮你什么
Help you with what?
你懂的
You know...
我称之为解脱
call it quits.
死
Die?
是的
Yeah.
船到桥头自然直  伙计
Cross that bridge when we come to it, mate, eh?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
布里特会想你的
You know, Britt'd miss you.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我也许会怀念你五分钟
I'd probably miss you for about five minutes.
知道么  你们是唯一
You know, you guys are the only reason
让我舍不得离去的原因
I've stuck around as long as I have.
雷  你好啊
Ray. How are you?
你怎么没来俱乐部
How come you didn't come to the club?
抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
完全忘了  我的错
Totally forgot. My fault.
你是要邀请我进去  还是
So, you gonna invite me in or...?
当然了  进来  进来
Yeah, 'course. Come in, come in.
发生什么了
So, what's been happening?
没什么事
Oh, not much.
你怎么样
What's been happening with you?
确实有点事
Oh, mate, heaps, actually. Yeah.
我昨天参加了试镜
I, um, had an audition for a pilot yesterday.
有点兴奋
So, pretty stoked about that.
- 是类似于电视秀吗  - 是的
- Like a TV show?  - Yeah.
你是来拿钱的吗
You here for the dough?
不  就是想过来看看
No, just thought I'd come around
你的演艺事业进展如何了
and see how your acting career is going.
好吧
Yeah.
伙计  我周三会给你的
Uh, mate, I'm gonna have to get that to you on Wednesday.
你之前说你会有钱的
Said you'd have the money, man.
我知道  我确实有
No, I know. I know I did.
很抱歉  但是到周三的时候
And I'm sorry, but I'm definitely gonna have it
我肯定就会有钱了
by Wednesday. Definitely.
那我也得教训你一下了
I have to give you a touch-up.
什么  还有两天就周三了啊
What? But Wednesday's two days away.
我知道周三是什么时候
Yeah, I know when Wednesday is.
好吧
Okay.
能不打脸吗
well, could it not be the face?
一定要是脸
It's got to be the face.
为什么
Why?
一定要是某处别人能看到的地方
It's got to be somewhere where people can see it.
为什么
Why?
这样要是弗雷迪看到你
So, if Freddy sees you,
他就知道我是在干活的
he knows I've done my job.
好吧
Okay.
同意了
Cool?
- 好的  - 好
- Yep.  - All right.
请别用我的尤克里里琴
Don't-don't use my uke, please.
是我奶奶给我的
My nan gave me that.
高兴了
Happy?
- 好  - 好的
- Yeah.  - Cool.
别躲啊
Don't flinch, all right?
那是我妈  就只是我妈而已
Mate, mate, it's just my mum. It's just my mum, okay?
- 求你了  - 你为什么不早说
- Please. Pl...   - Why didn't you fucking say something?
她和我要待上几天
She's staying with me for a couple days.
求你了
Please?
你好
Hello.
How you doing?
老妈  这是雷  是我的好兄弟
Mum, this is Ray. He's a mate of mine.
嗨  我是罗琳
Hi. I'm Lorraine.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
我去泡杯茶
Well, I'm gonna make a cuppa.
你们要吗
Would you boys like one?
好的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks, love.
皮皮节
年度医学美肤大促 9.9-9.29
新氧
医美
■
新人199元免单
○
-
你是做什么的  雷
So, what do you do, Ray?
安保工作
Security, mainly.
你就来这住几天
So, you're just here for a couple of days,
- 是吗  - 是的
- are you?  - Yes.
其实我现在住在布罗肯希尔
I'm actually living in Broken Hill at the moment.
去了那边好几年了
Been there a few years now.
我几年前去过
I went through there a few years ago.
很漂亮
Nice, uh...
感觉挺好的
It's got a good feel to it.
是的  很漂亮
Yeah, it's nice.
那有一种真正的社区的感觉  我很喜欢
It's got a real community feel about it, which I like.
是啊  在这附近可没有类似的地方  是吧
Yeah, well, you don't get much of that around here, do you?
确实
No, you don't.
我告诉你
I lived in St Kilda for many years,
我曾住在圣基尔达很多年
and there's very little community spirit there,
那里几乎没什么社区精神
I can tell you.
我们最好走了
We better get going.
该死  没错
Oh, shit. Yeah.
我们要去接我妹妹下班了  那个
Um, we got to pick up my sister from work, so...
其实  老妈
Actually, Mum,
我和雷
um, me and Ray--
我们要为我的试镜彩排
we've got to r-rehearse for an audition I've got.
- 又有试镜  - 是的
- Oh, another one?  - Yeah.
没事吧
So... is that all right?
没事
Yeah. That's fine.
我开我的车去
I'll take my car.
- 很好  - 我帮你开门  亲爱的
- Great.  - Oh. I'll get that door for you, love.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你  雷
Nice to meet you, Ray.
好的
Okay.
祝好运
Oh, and... break a leg.
会的  谢谢
I will. Thanks.
别打牙就行
Just-just not the teeth.
我花了八千块买的镶饰
Hey? I've just spent eight grand on veneers.
- 还有什么要求吗  - 没了
- Anything else?  - No, that's it.
别打了
Oh... I've got it!
别打了  我去拿钱
I've got it! I've got the fucking money.
别打了
I've got it.
该死
Fuck!
为什么你不在之前我问你要的时候
Why didn't you just give me the fucking money
就给我钱
when I asked for it?
我要去洛杉矶参加试镜啊
I'm going to L.A. for pilot season.
不  你不用了
No, you're not.
别  别  别
No, no, no, no, no, no!
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另招募长期居住海外的CC字幕录制童鞋（有酬劳）
联系QQ：864413459 注明：CC录制
我说漂亮的人啊
* I said beautiful people *
他们的旅行袋里有一件罗伯特·帕默的T恤
* They've got a Robert Palmer T-shirt in their travel bag *
漂亮的人
* Beautiful people *
他们头上都有个价格
* They've got a price upon their head *
我说漂亮的人啊
* I said beautiful people *
你有刚从洛杉矶飞来的朋友
* Have got some friends who just flew in from L.A. *
漂亮的人
* Beautiful people *
他们不怎么说话
* They haven't really much to say *
我说  人们  他们只是想带走你
* I said, people, they just want to take you *
人们  他们只是想约束你
* People, they just want to make you *
人们  他们只是让你崩溃
* People, they just want to break you down *
他们只是想把你打倒
* They just want to take you down. *